Guide to the Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers, Circa 1976-1990 MS2188
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Nadine P. Winter Council of the District of Columbia papers
Circa 1976-1990
1985-1990
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Winter, Nadine P.
MS2188
58 Linear Feet
This collection contains the constituent files of Nadine P. Winter during her time as a member of the Council of the District of Columbia representing Ward 6. These records date in the 1980s through 1990.
Biographical/Historical note
Nadine P. Winter served as the Council of the District of Columbia member representing Ward 6 from 1975 to 1990. Ms. Winter moved to Washington, D.C. in 1947 and soon after began her work in social action and social services for the residents of the residents in Northeast and Southeast Washington. She holds degrees from Brooklyn College (NY), Cortez Peters Business School and a Masters of Arts Degree from Federal City College. Ms. Winter is the founder and former Executive Director of Hospitality House, Inc. Under her leadership, Hospitality House, served the underpriviledged residents of Washington, D.C. with day care for youth and seniors as well as running a temporary homeless shelter. Ms. Winter was also a proponent of the concept of Urban Homesteading. She was one of the original organizers of the National Welfare Rights Organization. Ms. Winter's involvement in politics included serving as a delegate to the Democratic National Convention, as a member of the National Democratic Women's Club and the District of Columbia Women's Political Caucus.
Arrangement note
Organized into six series: Constituent correspondence and services, Government business and correspondence, Personal and office files, Political correspondence with or concerning institutions and issues, Environmental issues, and Community development /Ward Six.
Scope and Contents note
The materials in this collection include correspondence, publications, legislative bills, and meeting minutes. These documents all relate to the work of Nadine P. Winter as a member of the Council of the District of Columbia and most of the files contain correspondence from constituents and Ms. Winter's response and the action she is prepare to take on their behalf. These records are dated from the 1980s through 1990.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Gift of Nadine P. Winter, 1992.
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for research.
Washington (D.C.) Politics and government; Housing; City council members -- Washington (D.C.); Winter, Nadine P.; District of Columbia. Ward 6.; District of Columbia. City Council.
- Constituent correspondence and services, Circa 1985-1990; Series 1
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence with Winter's consituents. The topics within this series include among others: abandoned buildings, drug trafficking, public works projects/needs (road repair, garbage collection, traffic lights, etc), opinions on bills, constituent service request forms, and constituent service fund
  Arrangement note
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Constituent Service Request Forms, 1989 January; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Constituent Service Request Forms, 1989 February; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Contituent Service Request Forms, 1989 March; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Aamot, Jacqueline, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Abdus-Salum, Salum, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Abrahams, Edward, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Abrams, Carl, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acree, DE, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adams, GR, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Adams, Clifford, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Adams, Elizabeth, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Adams, James, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Adams, Mildred, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Adams, Nicholas, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Aikens, Antonell, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agle, Collie, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Ahlfeld, Mary, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Aki-El, Jamal, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Akridge, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alexander, Douglas, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Alfonso, Pedro, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Allen, David, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Allen, LaVerna, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Allen, Thomas, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Allston, Amu, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Alston, Doris, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Alson-El, William, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Altmon, Bradford, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Amendolia, James A., 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arner, Robert, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Anderson, Carol, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Anderson, Bernadette, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Anderson, Cynthia, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Anderson, Evangeline, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Anderson, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Anderson, Keith, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Anderson, Raleigh, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Anderson, Shirley, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Anderson, Thelma, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Anderson, William, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Angerame, Anthony Arnold, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Anonymous, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Anonymous, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Appell, Stephen, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Appleton, John, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Arline, Ralph, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Armstrong, Joyce, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Armstrong, Page, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Armwood, David, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Ashley, Ruth, 1988; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Ashley, William, 1990; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Ashley-Goodwin, Charlese, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Ashmore, Anne, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Ashton, Vivian, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Atkins, Katherine, 1984; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Austin, Karen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Aylor, Richard, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Baffer, Barbara, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bagley, Bob, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bailey, Ms. Betty, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Robert, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Baken, Denise, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Michael, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Baltimore, Harold, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Balz, Nancy, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Banks, Isadore, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ball, Donald, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Barbour, Gertrude E., 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Barbour, Obie (Disability Claim DHS), Undated; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Barkley, Charmaine, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Barnes, Lisa, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Barnes, Donald, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Barnes, Ms. Mary G., 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Barnes, Georgiana, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Barnes, Veronica, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Barnes, William, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Barnett, Karen, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Barry, Gene, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Barsotti, Larry, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Bartley, Anne, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Barton, Shari, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bass, Dennis, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bates, W, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Battle, Cyntia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Battle, Joe, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Battle, Percy, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Baxter, James, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bayne, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Beasley, Edward A., 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Beaver, La Juan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Becker, Joseph F., 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bedney, Osceola N., 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Beeman, Josiah, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Begle, Frances, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Bell, Ella, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Bell, Orlando, 1985; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Bell, Timothy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bellamy, James, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bellinger, Daniel, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bellis, Alice, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bello, Panchito, 1987; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Belisiore, Natasha, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Benjamin, George, 1988; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Benson, Beverly J., 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Benson, Joseph, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Benson, William, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Benton, Wiley, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Berg, Jeff, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Berman, Jay, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Berman, Randi, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bernard, Douglas, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Bernero, Raymond J., 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Bernstein, Betty, 1990; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Berntson, Bryon, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Berry, John, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Berry, Terran, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Berton, Bernard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Berton, Bernard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Beasley, John, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Bethea, Simon, 1986; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Bethea, Robert, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Better, William, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bigelow Houghton, Robert, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Billiops, Brenda, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Billups, Lynne, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - bindord, John D., 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Birbaum, Marie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Blacksher, Ashley K., 1985; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Blackson, Noomi Condace, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Blackwell, Peter, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Blackwood, Rolan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Black, Barbara, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Blackman, Mary, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Blaine, Robin, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Blaine, Robin, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Blakeslee-Collin, Carol, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Blesi, Sam, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Blue, Portia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Bobo, Emanuel, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Boddie, Wilburn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Bohen, Jean, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bolden, Ellen B., 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bonds, George, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Booker, Felix, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Boone, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Boose, Carolyn, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Boraks, Jacqueline, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Bostick, Ida, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Boutte, Mary, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bowden, Ernest, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bowie, Christal, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Boules, Ray, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Boules, JC, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Bowlins, Carolyn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bowmen, Trudie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bown, Mary, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bowser, Joseph, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Boxley, Diane, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Boyd, Daisy, Undated; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Boyd, Roberto, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Boyd, Wesley, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Boyer, Lynn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Boyle, Donald, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Boyle, Joan, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Branch, Lawrence, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bradford, Albert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Bradlee, Benjamin C., 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Bradley, Bob, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Brand, Richard, 1989; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Brandon, Walter A., 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Brannock, Lisa, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Brannum, Robert, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Bray, Andrea, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Brazil, Harold, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Bream, Carolyn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Brian, Kim, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Briachouse, Dennis, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Brisbon, Thomas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bristol, Jane, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Brook, Ann, 1986; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Brooks, Alphonso, 1988; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Brooks, Christine, 1990; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Brooks, Maria, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Brooks, Anthony, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Brooks, Jo, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Brooks, Alphonso, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Colleen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Brown, Floyd, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brown, Floyd, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Gail, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brower, Carol, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brown, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brown, Leroy, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Brown, Alfred, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Brown, Gladys, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Brown, Bernice, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Brown, Ann, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Brown, Floyd, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Brown, Levy, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Browne, Howard, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Brown, Synthia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Browne, RD, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Broyles, Joan, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Bruck, Ronald, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bryant, Joseph, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Brunstein, S, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Burton, Rudolph, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Bucchanan, Karissa, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Buckalew, John, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Buckley, Constance, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Buckley, Helen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Buckner, CD, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Buckner, Gloria, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Buell, Julie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Bullock, William, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Bunting, Lemuel, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Burges, Bill, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Burka, David, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Burke, Rebecca, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Burke, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Burks, Audrey, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Burmeister, Jon, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Burnett, Mattie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Burnett, Carol, Undated; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Burrows, Alicia, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Burton, Phyllis, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Busby, Venera, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Bush, Alice, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Butler, Anne, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Butts, Reginald, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Butler, CL, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Butler, Helen, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Butler, Danny, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Butler, Thelma, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Butler-Truesdale, Sandra, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Bullock, Vonique, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Butler-Turner, Catherine, 1989; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Bynum, Leola, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Byrd, Cameron, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Byrd, Jerry, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Byrd, Mary, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Byrd, Toye, 1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Byrne, Julianne, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Cain, James, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Calloway, Angelique, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Calvin, Bernice, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Cameron, Joe, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Cameron, Tom, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Camp, Mamie, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Campbell, Altha, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Campbell, Mamie, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Campbell, Plater, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Capozzi, John, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Cantrell, Barbara, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Carol, Janice, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Carr, Dana, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Carr, Dorothy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Carr, Edith, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Carroll, Jeannette, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Carroll, Stanley, 1983; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Carter, Colonel V., 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Carter, Earlette, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Carter, Joe, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cartwell, Helen, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Case, Harlow R., 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Cate, Thomas J., 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Cereletty, Marie M., 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Chamberlin, Mimi, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Chambers, Clifton, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Chan, William, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Chandler, Edith, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Chaney, Donald, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Chapman, Anna, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Chapman, Kenneth Mr. & Mrs., 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Chapper, Edith, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Charles, Marion, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Chase, Althea, Undated; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Chase, HS, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Cherry, BM, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Chevalier, Jacques, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Chilton, Marilyn, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Chorlton, Tom, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Citz, J, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Clark, Annie, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Clark, Fred J., 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Clarke, Craig, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Clarke, Cynthia, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Clarke, Doris, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Clarke, Lavinia, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Clarke, Leroy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Clarke, Lesley, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Clark, Lucille, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Clarke, Virginia, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Cleary, Mary, 1985; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Cloyd, Tawana, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Coad, Gail, 1987; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Coates, David, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Coblyn, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Cochran, James, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Cohen, Linda, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Cohen, Phil, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Cohn, Thomas, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Cole, Ametro, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Collins, Monore, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Cole, Jewel, 1989; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Cofuld, Roscoe, 1990; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Concerned Citizens of 9thSt. NE, 1986; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Constituent Service Fund, 1988; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Coronado, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Cory, Robert H., 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Cox, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Crawford, Etheline, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Crawford, HR, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cropp, Linda, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Crosby, Robert, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Crowe, Adrian, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Crum, Paulette, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Crump, Evetta, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Culbert, Mildred, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Culbertson, C, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Culp, David, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Culver, Charles, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cunningham, Larry, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Cunningham, Larry, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Curran, Gary, 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Currie, Karen, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Curtain, Raymond, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Cyrus, Quindene Wendy, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Dale, Diane, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Dalrymple, James, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Dameron, Ken, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Darling, Joseph, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Davidson, Alan, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Davie, DD, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Davis, Carolyn, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Davis, Delores, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Davis, Dorothy, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Daniels, Edward, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Davis, Elizabeth, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Davis, Edwin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Edwin, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Davis, Evelyn, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Davis, Mark, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Davis, Melvin, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Davis, Pauline, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Davis, Sydney, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Davis, Tonya, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Day, Lawrence, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - De Guzmon, Diane, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Delbruegge, John, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - DeMarco, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - DeLoach, Perry, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - DeMott, Albert, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Dempsey, Joseph, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Denton, Don, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Deqwittner, Brian, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Deskins, Merrill F., 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Deskins, Tanya, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Dews, Peola, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Dickerson, Ella, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Dickerson, Lilliam, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Diggs, Charles Jr., 1988; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Diggs, Shirley, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Dillion, Dorothy Dr., 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Dinan, Don, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Dinkins, Jr., 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Ditano, Ralph, 1989; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Dixon, Arrington, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Dixon, Dexter, 1987; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Dixon, Sharon, 1990; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Dobbs, George, 1986; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Dodge, Chris, 1988; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Dolbeare, Louis, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Dolgosh, Kathryn M., 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Donaldson, Betty, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Donovan, David, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Donovan, Donald, 1987; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Dorsey, George, 1989; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Douglas, Scott J., 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Dovault, Bobby, 1986; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Dove, Clifton, Undated; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Downey Katherine, 1980; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)